TL/n: First time subtitling anything.
Let me know of any
inconsistencies in translations
I was dreaming...
of when I met you
in the 2nd year of high school
That...
Fantasy-like day of a dream
Thank you for waiting
I'll let you know when the bride is ready
Excuse me...
Are the bride's sisters here?
Yes
They've been here for quite a while
I see...
Excuse me sir, the bride is calling for you
What's up?
I'll be ready in a moment, wait there
Oh yeah, apparently they're here
Jeez, whatever are they planning this time
They haven't changed since high school
Troublemakers, all of them
I was dreaming again, huh?
I wonder how many times I've seen it
For it to be that burnt into my memory
What a crazy nightmare
Thanks for waiting!
Am I still sleeping?
I love you (x5)
Yotsuba!
Leave it to me!
Yeah!~
Today was another big win
thanks to you girls
Especially Yotsuba,
you've been improving quite a lot recently
Huh, me?
You think so?
I doubt that happens
since we're quintuplets
No, you can't deceive my eyes
Take her as an example and
practice just as hard
An.. Example.. hmm
Since the game ended, lets hurry
The store is gonna close
Oh, you have some shopping to do?
Yeah!
We're gonna buy a present for mom
A gift for recovering
We all saved our allowance for this day
Well then
Lets head to the flower shop!
Ichika is in too much of a hurry, ha-ha
Well, lets go
I wonder
what flowers would mom
be the happiest with
I once heard that the carnation
is the best for moms
Carnation?
I don't really understand it myself
Yotsuba, how much did we have?
Hmm...
Wait... I might've dropped the wallet
Ah!
Anything over there?
Nothing here
It should be around here if we still
had it before soccer
I'm going to look a bit further
Yotsuba...
Oh no...
It's all my fault...
What do I do?
I'm sorry everyone
It's all my...
Don't beat yourself up
It could've been any of us
Someone's mistake is everyone's fifth
Everyone...
This isn't meant to be compensation but...
I found a pretty flower earlier
What... do you think...?
Yotsuba, is that...?
Sorry...
I shouldn't justify myself
We all found this flower as well
I guess we're just quintuplets
I'm home
Anyone there?
Welcome home mom!
We're all happy that you're doing well
Here, we got you this
Thank you for everything
How was work today?
Oh, she's frozen
Maybe this wasn't...
To me...
The five of you being
healthy is all I desire
Thank you
I think we're done here
Let's go home
You think...
dad left that there?
No way
Our last summer in high school
went by so fast
When the second semester begins
We'll be busy preparing
for the school festival
Ichika, you're gonna be absent
from school for a while right?
I've got a movie shoot
Is your attendance fine?
Somehow
Fuutarou said he can give
me private lessons
Even so
I never thought we'd come back here
Evicted half a year after moving
We're really unlucky
Whoa
It's still so clean
Did Ebata-san keep it like this?
Has (s)he been cleaning all along?
It's spacious and nice
Thank you for your time
Oh, Itsuki!
What were you doing in
the teachers' office?
There was something I didn't
understand in today's class
So I went to ask
I see
I had some questions
about the school festival
They just left the decision to the
class presidents
Hmm
Speaking of class presidents
I wonder what Uesugi-san
thinks of these festivals
Apparently, 3rd years'
supposed to do stalls
Fried chicken and sausages
Buttered baked potato is good too
Sorry
Can we continue this later?
It's almost time to help out at cram school
I thought Itsuki would be hooked
Did everyone go home?
Oh, its just Yotsuba
Sorry for bothering you
Is it about the food stalls?
Give me a minute
I can't waste any time now
Ah right
Raiha showed me
The ad Ichika did
It'll be a summer...
...you wont forget
She's already a celebrity
She made her dream come true
Itsuki said she was
aiming to be a teacher
What a crazy goal
Yotsuba
Yes?
Do you have goals for the future?
So sudden...
I've never thought of it
Well...
You are extremely athletic
There are many options in that direction.
I kept you waiting
I'm going around to ask
about last year's stall data
Is it alright?
You said you can't waste any time
That's exactly why
It's the last school event
I'm not wasting any time
That's why if I'm going to do it,
I'm going to thoroughly enjoy it
Time is finite
No matter how much you have,
it's never enough
I'm counting on you
Alright
Leave it to me!
These are... The food stall menus
that were popular last year
If you have any other suggestions
Please let us know
I'll vote for takoyaki
It's better to just follow the trend
and...
You gathered that information, right?
If its takoyaki, I can show off
my skills that I got from work
Sounds like fun
disagreement noises
Any other ideas?
I wanna do Taiyaki!
Tapioca!
Miku... any thoughts?
Pancakes
Umm...
I don't think anyone did that last year
It could work
Nice idea
Thank you Miku!
I like the idea too
I think it'll be cute!~
That's all for today
We'll discuss this later
Nakano-san
Are we allowed to perform on this stage?
Absolutely!
The sewing club made some outfits
I wonder if the customers will come
Wow, Its amazing!
If you already have a spot
I can put up some posters
Please allow me to help
Thank you
Yotsuba is quite popular
Why doesn't anyone come to me for help
Expectations
I'd like to send some
invitations to family
Already prepared!
Invitations
Even so, stalls
No matter what we make, I'll be excited
Yes, exciting
Are you seriously planning to cook?
People all over the place
are coming to visit
Worst case all the nearby
residents get food poisoning
I'm improving, you know?
Besides, you'll be there
So I'm not worried
Of course
If you make it with me
There is no such thing as a single failure
Thanks for the wait
Great work
Are you not overworking yourself?
This is the last event
I don't want even a millimeter
of regret this festival
Last... huh...
Fuutarou
I had you come all the way
here to help me study, but...
Do you have enough time for exam studies?
Preparing for the school festival
seems to be time consuming
Actually, today...
I got my evaluation results
for my desired school
Do..don't look
I don't want this to be seen
So it's good, right?
That's no fun
In case you didn’t know...
The only person we weren't doubting
was you, who has always studied
Please take care of everyone
This is the crucial point
Don't worry
I'm sure both my studies and
the school festival will go well
Just watch
We'll make it the best school festival
Boys, just give up already!
Why don't you girls give up?
Everyone loves fluffy pancakes
Miku-chan, tell em!
Uh... umm...
You saw last year's data, right?
There is no Japanese who dislikes takoyaki
Right, Nino-san?
Sure...
But Nino-san, you said you like pancakes
Why are you on their side?
That's a lie, right?
It can't be helped
I was the one who suggested it first
I'll take responsibility till the end
And...
Making something and
eating is a different story
That Fluffy soufflé
pancake you speak of
I even fail sometimes
This argument is going nowhere
We just have to do both
I didn't expect the class to split
up about something so trivial
Exactly
Why did you have to bring up pancakes?
Apparently Fuutarou's mother
often made pastry
And...
If you remember our past
Yeah, I understand
That was the definition of fluffy
But... that can't be mastered overnight
You've tried before?
It's the first dish I tried
I still think takoyaki is much easier
All the more for a food stall
Even so...
You didn't have say it so straight
I hate not doing things straightforward
Hmm
Nino, Miku
Oh the two of you were together
Fuutarou
Did something happen?
No, it's fine
I'm quite busy now but...
It's a festival
Lets enjoy it
What was that for?
I have something to tell him
You can go home ahead
Miku?
Fuutarou
Hm?
What's up?
Before the school festival,
there's something I want to say
Really?
I have something to say to you too
Can I hear it first?
Yeah... I heard that
Your evaluation test
Was an A
Congratulations!
It's been a long road
But everything will pay
off if you get into College
I think it was worth teaching you girls
Yeah, yeah
Hey Fuutarou,
Go out with me
Ah! Sorry
I didn't mean it like that
Let's go out to a few places this Sunday
Ah?
Oh?
Are you heading home?
Pretty much
Looking for someone to go home with
Oh really
I apologize then
I'm going directly to the cram school
Ah, alright
You're very determined
Umm...
How was your evaluation?
It wasn't as bad as I thought
I think it was a B
Wait, what?!
What do I do, Nino?
I put in my all, but
This is my results, The road
ahead is pitch black
I'm just trying to be like mom, after all
Me trying to be a teacher
is a fantasy in a fantasy
Please calm down
Sorry for troubling you
The teacher said I should
discuss it with my parents
But...
I guess he isn't much help
No...
I don't mean it that way
I don't want to worry our father any more
Worry?
When has he ever?
The only reason we got this
far was thanks to our father
At least, that's how I see it
That flower was definitely from our father
Although he seldom
does anything directly
I think he's always cared about us
I doubt that
At least to start...
I'll discuss it with Shimoda-san
And sometime soon
A special class will be held
by a famous lecturer
Nino
I'm preparing the invitation
you mentioned earlier
I changed my mind
Is that okay?
I must've lost myself for a moment to
think papa would want an invitation
I thought it was a good idea
He wouldn't come anyway
He rarely even shows up at home
Sneaking through some random shadow
That a bit harsh
But...
Those are the girls who were glaring at me
Let's turn back before
we get into trouble
I understand what you're trying to say
In short
It's strange that Nino
is in the boys' group
She's buttering up
Since she must be after some boy
Exactly!
If that "some boy" was yuusuke...
And Nino was his girlfriend...
I've got no chance
Sakura...
Cheer up
You've misunderstood
Nino's type is not in the takoyaki group
I know that much
don't worry
I don't believe you
How are you supposed to know that?
Because the class president
is in a neutral position
I can't vote for either
I don't understand
What does that have
to do with this?
Yeah (x2)
Nino actually likes...
likes ME!
So uhh... try to get along, okay?
Uesugi-kun
Let's not fall into a delusion
I'd feel bad for Nino if
that fantasy spread
Nn..NO!
I really mean it
I don't think it's bad to
sneak in the shadows
There must be some reason
Yotsuba...
Help me think of what to
write in the invitation letter
I don't remember allowing you to enter
Please find your way to the exit
Hey, don't be so distant with me
I came to give you good information
He's returned
It's been over a decade
This one is An-chan
The one behind is San-chan
Now here's a question...
What was this little one's name?
Everyone has the same face
You couldn’t tell the difference
I really wanna get this right
That's correct!
Although its natural they look similar
since these five are all sisters
It's just like you girls
Now that you mention it,
that one feels like Nino
Then are you that one?
Fuutarou... D:
Fuutarou
I want to study cooking
So I can't go to college
I'm sorry Fuutarou
I see...
I will support you if
that's what you choose
That's quite the conflicted
look on his face
You're right...
Vocational schools...
I guess that works
I don't think it would be
wrong to go to college
But I don't know what's correct
But...
I can't help but want
to pursue my dreams
This is all I wanted to tell you
Since you a special person to me.
Is that...
Of course
I mean it like that
Miku saying this now
Makes me feel this wasn't
just about career paths
I told you what I wanted to
It's your turn next, Fuutarou
What I have to tell them is...
Welcome home brother
Why are you here?
Here it is
Yotsuba says she doesn't
remember giving you one.
Oh... thank you
The curry is ready!
May I join?
Do you have time to be
doing this right now?
I know about your evaluation
That doesn't mean I've
given up on that school
I'll study even harder, even if
it makes me miss the festival
I hope so
I'll have problems if you don't pass
If you fail after all this,
my efforts would feel wasted
Even so, I don't think it'll be meaningless
Ichika, who aimed to be an actress
And Miku, who's aiming to be a chef
Do you think the time you
spent was meaningless?
I guess you're right
Our relationship is already
beyond tutor and students
Uesugi-kun
Even if failure awaits
None of us will regret
coming to this school
Or meeting you
This relationship...
It wasn't meaningless
Now...
It's my turn
__ ___ _____ ___ __ ___ ________...
On ___ _____ __ ___ ________...
On the _____ __ ___ ________...
On the first ___ __ ___ ________...
On the first day __ ___ ________...
On the first day of ___ ________...
On the first day of the ________...
On the first day of the festival...
To all our guests, please
gather at the gymnasium
...__ ___.
...At ___.
...At 3pm.
We will now commence the opening ceremony
to the 29th annual Asahi
high school Sunrise Festival
On the first day of the festival
____ __ ___ _________ at 3pm.
come __ ___ _________ at 3pm.
On the first day of the festival
come to ___ _________ at 3pm.
come to the _________ at 3pm.
On the first day of the festival
come to the classroom at 3pm.
Sent.
To begin, an opening act from a
few of our female students
Nino is awesome!
I'm surprised she's doing this
The 29th Sunrise Festival
Has begun!
Whoa you're good!
Who taught you?
At my part-time job
Oh! Customers!
Thank you
I wonder if I can take a break by 3pm
Alright!
is that it for the inspections?
Hey, Yotsuba!
OOHH!! It's the red one!
The opening dance was so cute!
I've become a fan!
Please try our corndogs!
Thanks...
I wanted to go see how
the food stalls were doing
I wonder if Ichika
always goes through this
Nino!
Oh... it's just you, Itsuki
That was a splendid dance
It really set the mood for this festival
It doesn't look like
you're at a festival
Rest assured, I will finish it by 3pm
I'm beat
I wonder what Fuu-kun is doing
It's right this way
Thanks for the directions
You are a wonderful young man
Uesugi-kun
I want to make this place a rest area
How should I go about it?
O.. Okay...
Thanks for waiting
Hey, Miku!
You're late!
Anyway, it looks like everyone is here
No, just one more
Ichika!
You came!
Why didn't you let us know?
I'm amazed it didn't cause a huge fuss
Yeah, somehow
Now we really have everyone here
It's nice having everyone together
I feel the same
Since everyone's here
why don't we eat?
I bought a lot from the food stalls
I was holding back the whole day!
I love all five of you
No beating around the bush?
What does that mean?
I would be great if...
The 6 of us could stay like this forever
But...
I think I have to give an answer
Fuutarou...
Go ahead
Alright
Although
I think it'd be inappropriate to say
this in the middle of the festival
I'm not quite done
organizing my end either
Give me till the last day
Wait, what?
I'm kind of disappointed
How about a toast to but that aside?
Dibs on the orange juice!
Where is the matcha soda?
There is none
To put it simply...
It took quite a while
For you to solve this conundrum
Pleast don't tease me
But...
I envy you
Here's your drink
Well then
To celebrate the conclusion
Of a successfuly first day
Cheers!
Hello everyone!
Today's the Second day
of the Sunrise Festival
Today we are going to be
interviewing visitors on-the-spot
Are you watching, Nakano-san?
You still remember me, right?
I came here to see you
//////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
BEYOND THIS POINT IS JUST VOICE-TO-TEXT GOOGLE TRANSLATED, IT PROBABLY WONT MAKE SENSE
sorry
Excuse me
regained his composure
I don't know what you're looking for
is it me
I
to see a childhood friend
no work today
Dashi
School festival
have fun
nothing to enjoy
I don't have money to eat and walk
that kind of
late curly child
It hurt
You've grown up
When
Kubogi
Hmm
It's right
so more left
What
you're noisy next to me
Hey
want
hey hey
world
you told us that yesterday
Dating another thing today
is it
Uesugi-san can't even be in the corner
if you say
came here
Eh
Garne
What do you think
Wind
pancake
is
world
Hey
country is my class
It's a stall of
always my boo
Take care of Taro
God
It's like
Nice to meet you
My name is bamboo forest
Taro has been my classmate since elementary school.
We are classmates, but a teacher and a student
It's no exaggeration to say that the relationship is more than that of classmates.
chance encounter
is not it
I am Fuutarou too
to study
want to teach
is
When asked by a problem person who didn't listen
surprised
no
these are my students
and
yes
what
Then
It's clear now
me and you
which one is more intimate
four leaves
Me too
Tidying up is also a rag
Eh
Thank you
if it's true
We can indirectly say that we were indebted to you.
The time I spent with Uesugi seems to lose to you
However
That
I'm not going to lose when it comes to depth
Hmm
Please stop because it's difficult
and bamboo forest
don't tease me too much
These guys are my few friends
everyone is special
I'm getting really big
sorry both of you
pancake
one please
of
I have to cut corners on my work
my feelings
Because it will never change
Hmm
Tired
what do you think
Fuutarou was fine
All the quintuplets were good kids too
One
do your best
Wind Taro
this choice
or
I think I was right to make this choice
mosquito
people who think like that
three days
was too short
Hmm
this is
I want to confirm Asahi High School
in the item
in tragedy tulle
will also end
taxi
it's late
you know
Come to think of it, the Nakano family seems to be going to the same school.
drum
March
it was cute
me too
licking
chau
maybe i kiss
I was shocked
ok then
world
sometimes that happens
that's why
right
Even Fuutarou-kun has experienced it.
why you
But that was an accident
For real
and flew
and
with who
I don't understand
At that time, everyone sent it back with a lid.
death
who do you think
taxi
Came
You saved my life
you know
Because I might not be able to come to the school festival of
don't listen to the answer
Kana
If you're still confused, I understand
no one chooses
that's my answer
Don't say sweet things forever
world
Then
this is it
is
Are you okay
Then
I'm not used to doing something
good luck today
Hotel
let's go back to sleep
first section chief
or
director
just left the store
my sister is a towel
It seems
I want to feel safe and healthy
of is
I'm resting well
of
Kazetaro-kun
Your family came too.
I called you but I couldn't stay
how is everyone
I've just calmed down
We're fine, so don't worry
soccer
Was good
I haven't cleaned up yet, so I'm going back to school
B.
you send me a day
oh
tea
I'm going home today
Kazetaro
has finished today's work
Hmm
Then
walk a little
Hmm
Then
It's surprisingly big here.
I remember Futaro
It's the venue for the fireworks display.
When the stalls and people are gone
It sure feels spacious.
It's not that I'm unmanned
I know
couple
It is said that there are many establishments during these three days.
Among them, the most amazing
food on the third day
vegetable
I thought Fuutarou-kun knew that and said that.
Do I look like someone who is swept away by the trend of the world?
once again
You look like you're in the second half, but I'm unexpectedly vulgar
When my companion sees a luxury car, I look into it
Tension after a long trip
Exploding or Yahoo at the summit
I said
do you remember well
Hey
That's cute though
yes
I don't value your honest feelings
that's why
Don't say no one chooses
I don't even know how I feel
I'm thinking too hard
I'm just trying not to think about it
yesterday's kiss
didn't you talk about
human miku
It's a problem with Yotsuba
Pooh
Who would you be happy to be Taro?
Hmm
it's a vending machine
I'll give you money, so buy what you like
Fuutarou-kun's drink is fine
the bench there
I'll be waiting for you at
What is it
2 teas
Name
Tea is mandarin orange
juice
is four leaves
coffee
when will come
yes
But I have to
what to do now
Kazetaro-kun
Hmm
I made you wait too long
I did it when I achieved it
I feel like you've always been like this
eldest son has eldest daughter
we had a hard time with each other
eh
did you see
lips
why
were you awake
why were you watching
is
kiss
did
someone in the people
Hey
maybe you
It's bitter
hmm
was me
deer
'Cause it's more real than it looks
You can tell the difference by making
ancestor
yes but
just for that mother
maybe you're used to acting
yesterday
the drama you mentioned
The other party is the child of the same actress
eh
kissing someone warm
what
now still ng
kana
that's why
you are the first
An event that can not be done easily with a classmate girl
so i won't remember
forgot to ask
Was delighted
what is it
eyes from the child
Cherish honest feelings
what
That's right
Pooh
It doesn't matter who Taro chooses
Kana feeling
It won't be quiet for a while yet
this is
I want to confirm Asahi High School
in the item
at
exit win
Well then
First day of school festival
congratulations on the successful completion
mother
Then
you
How long are you going to stand out like that?
I wanted you to see
everyone was so cute
that opening
ceremony
really i should have done
took over
You act nice to everyone and accept too many jobs
It seems that you are also a helper in the drama club.
stop before the limit is reached
world
My brother is still a fool
I guess
that's all
it's not the reason
I accepted this job
from the stage
I thought I could see the audience
What does it mean
we
I sent an invitation to my father.
There was no shadow, no shape
No good
originally in
I don't care
yes
Maybe
maybe come during this time
I wonder if I should go look at the stalls
hey
I haven't heard from you
You made such a bold confession
How can you be alone
I'll call you directly
stop it
hand
nice
I don't expect anything from below
you too
I mustered up the courage to send an invitation
can you convince me
let's believe and wait
is it
pancake
shop
from yesterday
Obviously more people
Somehow it seems that I came here and became a rumor
no
I heard from Uesugi-kun.
Min-chan's class
The store of
today
Then
come
You gave me
I
Not disappointed now
for a moment
I thought you were my father
ladies and gentlemen
thank you for your hard work
to this
Asahi High School within the year
end the second day
To do
Best store
da
wait no more
To
about this
no more
I'm not going
I sent you an invitation, Dad
didn't come
Even the slightest thought of us
not
Noyo
The school festival is tomorrow too
I don't like it either
If it doesn't come true anyway
I feel like I'll regret even the things I wished for
I don't know much about your family
All I know is that it's not a normal parent-child relationship
but on the contrary do you know
You're so wary of me
That's my father's melon
bread
Dano
I can't do it without my love for you guys
That's why I'm complaining
you're lazy
Nah
outside
I found someone who
After reviewing the video
There's someone who matches the traits you're looking for
today
where did you come from
like this
Work environment
smartphone
I am happy with the model
this is it
maternity leave
It looks like you came
what to do
it's good
Kun
Papa
take me to
what were you worried about
hand
answer
Without
Werner
is it hmm
Thanks
I came to return the daughter I borrowed
Why are you going home before you die today?
It will burn soon
please eat
i know you came to school
pancake
Is not it
surprisingly cheap to make
my daughters will love it too
I wanted to make it last
what the last
there is no such thing
quite
i can't thank you enough
but no more
your precious time
Don't pour it on me, who has a short life expectancy
Please don't say that
Lena
Because my teacher is my mentor
that she is a teacher
how many years ago she
and when you're gone
her daughters also grieve
is that so
I regret only those children
To see the growth of those children who are still small
my mission
Thank you very much
I will pamper you just a little more
When you leave the hospital
please let me have a feast
pancake
you too
i think you will like it
This article
made by
It was such a bad day for cooking
I'm trying hard to find what I'm aiming for
Mika
not only
we 5
We've all grown up since then
its growth
I want you to watch me by my side
Mr. Miss
stopped
Which
side
Nano
You have faced each other without running away
what
Even so, it's a lot
by myself
I can eat it all
Then eat with the whole family
what suddenly
but everyone
I'm sure you'll be happy
I'm glad
then i'm the toilet
To
Uesugi-kun was there
this is your plan
wrong
world
he brought me this far
what about that
Beyond the scope of tutoring
that i couldn't do
I'm glad I asked God
I think from the bottom of my heart
Impossible as a parent
I hope you take your relationship with your daughters seriously.
wish
thank you for today
and until now
so
what about tomorrow
Color
rice field
ship
what are you doing
I slipped a little
I'm going home
do that
Tingling
do
it was okay
mosquito
After all, at least have a scary dream
now
Hey
Hey you
i just wanted to say
Hanasaki How has the relationship between us sisters changed?
my feelings don't change
B.
let me be your tutor
can be
increase
I want to confirm this from former Asahi High School
in the item
End the tragedy sell in
of this
love of
we
because it's summer
I can't lose to men's takoyaki
Miki-chan
class
It's about a boy from
Let's get along without being stubborn
world
I'm sure you did it together
is fun
world
I wish I had the courage to say
Hey
Nah
Me
let's look over there
Uesugi
teeth
go to boys
hand
sneaky
text
start the
stop doing
rice field
Reconcile quickly
this time i will do the opposite
Can I go and check the enemy situation?
tomorrow
It's obvious to the boss guy
is
Oh
What should I do Futaro
if you could change
Maeda
Because you're in the opposing camp
I might be able to change their minds
devil
It's just my intuition
Believe it or not, it's a good posterity
I believe in Fuutarou
Nakano
of
other
pancake
leader of
is like the year
Takoyaki
one please
I'll enjoy having this
It's hot so be careful
Thank you
Hmm
n a
class
I want to feed the girls in
when the day is over
i will bring everyone
Boys' seriousness
I'm sure it should be conveyed to everyone
Such a thing
suddenly told
Those guys
I told you to serve takoyaki
for them
you guys honestly
Buried
Wind Taro
believe
i have to say
I'm sorry for saying this on the day
I don't want it to end like this, it should be the same feeling
Even after finishing everything and graduating
It was a school festival
Let's make it something everyone can enjoy
yes
Speaking
Maeda-kun fed Matsui-san, right?
Don't say
it's you
You're the only one running away
Even though I wanted Maruyama-san to eat it
Then
chestnut
I don't even have a guy who wants to eat me anymore
Mr. Nakano
for these guys
can i ask
of course
Thank you
All thanks to Fuutarou
i'm not doing anything
bangs moved
I got stronger
sorry 1
group
Takoyaki and stalls
Suspend store opening
i found sugi
People after all
was
Do not know
talking to a girl
Does anyone know
I don't know Asuka
I just pulled it out
we 5
A person
I liked
go to sleep
believe
But when we first met
I was told
Believe in what you love
no matter what
because i like futarou
Because I like Fuutarou
I believed and moved on
meat
It's been a day
class
It's a pity that the stall of
Wind Taro
follow me
rooftop
No entry during the school festival
I thought I wouldn't bother you here
rice field
na
You're laughing at us for not being able to charm us anyway, so who are you?
it's not the time to say that
It's bad that the boy caused the accident
If this
did you call
I'm sure you won't get in trouble here.
No
I'm the one who's bothering you
other grass
Miku-chan, how about this letter?
Say
body
During
Maintain and develop boys and girls forever
is also a high school student
I'm a college student next year
Aren't you ashamed to fight like this child?
pancake
Takoyaki can't have ups and downs
Of course men and women
both are delicious
both of you are doing your best
can't accept that
pay back debt
It's been no fun since day one
uncomfortable
I was patient
Hey
make
The girl is tired from working all the time
pancake
the back of the shop
get a boy to help
By the way
and
even if i'm good
fruit
somehow
Leave it to me
I will persuade
trust me
smartphone
it's impossible to repair
I voluntarily gave up on being a player myself
ON
I was taught by
meat
girl
Who
I was shooting
Hey
Childhood friend
Like
Nanoha
as the opposite sex
are friends
mosquito
Narayoshi
You've been holding back from listening to me
patience
what
I'm sorry you don't care about me like that
Do you get it
Then
kiss
big
I told you to refrain
with the current flow why
money
I will hear the answer later
No matter what kind of insurmountable wall appears
as long as you believe in yourself
I can go on forever
do not hesitate
this is
I want to confirm Asahi High School
four years old now
lower beard
tulle
will also end
Thank you
thank you
increase
emerald
even so far
It's a pity to finish you here
I'm under your control
rice field
I wondered what happened to the sheep
I'm glad I asked a senior to take the place of
is
mosquito
It was good to be of help
I have come
tired
There seems to be no problem with the freshness of the ingredients.
The hairstyles around here are dangerous, so please put them away
at this rate
it seems to be in time
thank you for helping
Medium service
have a ticket
eat
you did a good job
Yotsuba
Uesugi-san is a bean sprout, so please take a rest
I'm sorry
it's okay
let me through
I want to finish by 15:00
worried
I'm here
I won't move until you listen to me
I haven't said anything since that morning
shop
so power
does not come out
fried chicken
please eat well
Is it alright
i'm hungry
To
stomach
full
I have a patient
Yotsu
thank you
i'm glad you were here
What are you saying
Goya
is a mutual relationship
to you too
Just being recognized by Mr. Uesugi
I feel like it all pays off
Mr. Uesugi adds the answer
When
two more days
I can spend days like today
I'm sure
is
if you choose me
why
Stop quoting
We're
If you come for this day
After causing such an accident
I have no choice but to accept
warned it's dangerous
because it's straight
something
hey
Hey you
rice field
Wind Taro
friend of
isn't it
hospital
I was surprised to hear that you are here
I can't afford to do it at all
mosquito
don't worry about me
who is it anymore
there's still a lot left to do
da
hey
I have to hurry
Everyone in the drama club is in trouble
world
Chiba
of
world
the day is already over
6 in Kyoto
year ago
Was it you who met Futaro?
Hannah and
I was shown so many photos that I didn't want to.
pancakes earlier
When I asked my brother at the restaurant
I knew that I was the only one who got strayed that day
As expected of Uesugi-san's teacher
nice to meet you
this thing
Wind Taro
told to
please don't
Could I ask the reason
i don't want to be disappointed
Mr. Uesugi has always tried to do the right thing
I was obsessed with useless things
meaningless 6
was a year
he is of no use
only trouble
what is the meaning of my existence
Is that all
i am meaningless
I don't need someone
i know someone who said something similar
and that person is now
I'm starting to walk forward
you from the past
so that I can step forward
large
Mr. Uesugi
let me beat
I have to go
say what
everyone's home now
Who
Say
avoid the
Not just for outsiders
Since then, I have taken on many
people who annoyed
Me
but elected
It is said to be completely quiet until tomorrow
I'm not going to go to high school
sit down
I'll let you go
What happened at the school festival when you were gone
Our company
one
You're the head of the Japan track and field club.
I wanted to meet you
It seems that I have been watching since yesterday's performance
but
this costume play me
i remember these two
Bliss
two people of
Maybe
did you share the content?
It's not just these two
did you get hurt
it's your fault
not
I'm here for you
hold and hold
is
I wish I could have you once in a while
tags
Willing to
I'm the one who took care of you
We apologize for the inconvenience this time.
Last day
work for me
please
Oh
Leave it to me
Futaro Uesugi
It's been a while
I'm tired from many things today
do it later
Thank you for remembering your absolute promise
i couldn't protect
Sorry
i don't care about that
Taro don't care
more important than the past
now
I don't rely on my memories with you
Difficulty finding one's own value
that's why
this is the last
hmm
Awesome
dreamed a little
It's because of a lot of things that happened during the school festival.
dare to
you let me do it
It's the last memory
It's not the time to drag the past forever
I feel like I'm moving forward
and
this is
I want to confirm Asahi High School
in the item
at
win win also ends
you
That section was taken care of
Anyway
come
I can't believe I'm studying in such a festival
Kana
oh dear
enter university
teacher
I want to aim for
The same road as my longing mother
my mother is also a school teacher
Know
hey
I was her homeroom teacher
you look just like your mom when she was young
just like
distorted
She longed for me and proceeded to a teaching career that didn't suit her
I want to regret that until the end
my life
I was just wrong
if you're just following your mother
Oh
Recommend
do not do
brother
Fire at store
it's true that there was
teeth
That
Was there anyone injured?
don't ride it
by the way hood
tower
Didn't you see Omin around the school?
of
Nano
father
all day today
because you said
I couldn't see the six sounds
the beard is soft
of
An old man who seems to ride on the face even if it is upside down
I'm glad you came
what happened after that
maybe i should tell you too
that man
what is your business
I wonder if he was wondering when to tell you
your mother is a former student
Plus her ex-colleague
and
she is ex-wife
i mean i
it's your dad
Mr. Miss
i've always wanted to see you
When I was protecting the whole country as a lecturer, I always
I was thinking of you somewhere
when that happens
tv set
I saw Ichika-chan reflected in
Now it's time to enter the castle as a father
Is not it
I heard about you from your mother
As soon as I found out that the children in my womb were quintuplets
she disappeared
That time
what was her mother like
i love you
sorry
let me atone for my sins
from now on
As a father, I want to do what I can for my daughter.
don't get involved with us
I have a father
Nakano-kun
when mom died
let me introduce this to you
her daughter
follow the shadow of her late mother
I'm dropping advice on the same wrong path as my mother
that your school teacher is not right for you
you should know best
The love for you that I cannot overlook as a father
pushed me
valuable
na
how to say
Was it the same as usual?
Raw
It's been a while so I don't know why
your ex father
There is a suspicion that he had contact with Itsuki.
Hmm
Itsuki can't listen
Even though today was the last day
what's wrong
I've been stuck in my room since yesterday
artificial flowers
Wait
you're going to the moon
take it
is it ok
That's why you're my husband
i like that place
leave this to me
You Itsuki
Hmm
you
sleeping too much
Even though this doesn't mean anything
what am i doing
Don't worry about that mountain
Even though I'm saying something appropriate anyway, the foreign mother also said
Moon
you should never be like me
But I can't give up
I'm aiming for your mother
I
I wonder if there is
mosquito
Is that so
There's no point in becoming a teacher
Not all good students
in the world
I am reminded that there is an unimaginable idiot
my policy
even if you bend
have to get along
are involved with others
There is no doubt that you will be tired both physically and mentally
Some students will rebel
Even at times like that, I have to let you run away and keep facing each other
Really
it was hard
I'm tired
I will never become a teacher
but what happened
It's not worth listening to all the nonsense
it's your dream
how much headwind
But
You decide whether to proceed or not
is it my dream
i just want to be a mom
Before
I have been told by someone
Aiming for her mother and chasing her dreams
It's very different from chasing your mother for your dreams
if you can understand that
longing for parents
to aspire to
definitely not wrong
I
will be
I am me
if students want
There's only one thing I can do as a tutor
full support
do
That's it
I came up with a way to say
weather
please tell me
maybe
thank you
It's
I have to do something
today
woman teacher
world
I don't think Itsuki-chan will come.
I learned to listen to my father's words
Is it okay to say
even my father
don't make me laugh
You and
long time no see teacher
We're not the ones who need it
Mr. Mudo
abusive language
When
of
I'm glad I got a chance to apologize even for the subtleties
I put a lot of effort into Nakano Ward.
it wasn't down
thank you
your irresponsible behavior
bring me and my daughters together
how are people
with regards to responsibility
it looks like you can't do it either
That's why Itsuki-chan came here voluntarily
not the unreliable you
Bork
she is at
Itsuki-kun is here
what is he saying
take a good look
It would be nice to have Itsuki-kun at the airport
i am here
what do you mean
deceived
excuse me
but
i knew it was going to happen
What about it
I was just wrong
love can distinguish us
mother's words
is it about her again
come on
How long are you going to believe in such irrelevant rants?
forget now
so is your mother
it shouldn't be
she remember what she said
she said her mother had her regrets
she remembers
is
your mother was wrong
you will be
i don't think so
even if really
her mom denied her own life
i denied it
OK
am i not a mom
she has seen it
she gave up everything
mother figure
The life of such a kind person
can't be wrong
blurry
Hey, you speak like you know me.
then she has her children
You don't know how much hope I've found on your face
you're not qualified to talk about her
she is a woman
from you to the end
There was no word of apology to her mom
i won't forgive you
I won't be a can of atonement
The day will never come when you will be free from your mother
I've come all the way
unsightly
uncle
and
did you get it all done
it's you
I saw you from below
hey
mosquito
thank you
since mom died
to fill her loneliness
was trying to impersonate her mother
Before I knew it
The line between myself and my mother became blurred.
even my dreams
I lost my confidence
Me
mom
I don't have to
Nigate was the one who taught me
is
thank you
The sky is getting so dark all of a sudden
Ma
It's winter
eh
Chan
I passed
i feel sick
this is the case
sorry
anyway
It is thanks to you that I was able to have confidence
i'm not a mom
I just noticed something so simple
because you were there
my ideal teacher
stay with mom
nothing
in short
Uesugi-kun
you are my ideal
how much i wanted to hear
yes
Mr. Nakano and others
Sorry I made you wait
It was Itsukishima
I was told that it was that child by Fuutarou-kun
I could also say thank you to his father.
to everyone again i
good good
world
It was also a problem for our family.
can be
gatou
there is nothing but discomfort
Mikuni was even disguised
I do not care
in addition
I'm not satisfied with Honatsu's disguise
This child is this child with a mysterious pride
is also sprouting
Ordinary people just get it wrong
Even if the contents change, the face remains the same
How long will we be quintuplets
There's still time until the promise with Fuutarou-kun
You can change your mood and enjoy flavored vegetables
Hey
How long will I be sitting here
Somehow, the wind blows in the sky
street car
That's right
keep eating
death
There was a store I couldn't go to
When it's done I
I promise to meet you
I see
I just saw that island
When h-ko was also there 5
It was full of people.
Eh
Maeda-kun
I knew in that moment that you were a family member.
hey
oh dear
because it's a story
Ichinohe-san is the only one who vaguely understands
Uesugi-kun is of course
I can tell
Hey
He's not confident when you say that
At first I was more confused than now
I'm not good at remembering people's faces
Moreover
They take full advantage of it
feel free to use
how many times have you been deceived
They were in trouble until the end
from
the style of drawing
I suddenly wondered
Now you can tell from which of them
good
Yatai go
wait
as it is now
Takeda what's going on
What do you mean
Isn't it the climate for Uesugi-kun?
etc.
Uesugi-kun, don't hide the secrets among us
hand
if beautiful
Hey
Like
of
someone from the quintuplets
A student's duty is to study
Because I lived believing that everything else was unnecessary
I didn't need to throw anything else away
We also study
Work entertainment and romance
They're always full pitchers
I'm stuck
A series of people taught me that
Until I realized just that
I've kept you waiting until now
If I'm still the same as I used to be
I wonder if I was alone at this moment
Uesugi
good
Shall we go to the food stalls then?
curry
take it
but
hey
So I'm going to the stall
the shape really helps
Already
It has been decided
To enjoy this festival until the end
It's almost time
Ken UesugiWhen everything ends today
we
in each room
while holding each other's thoughts
I'm waiting for you
you're going
only one classroom
this proposal
I know it will get you in trouble
this is our resolution
please
please understand that
this
To
red mark
each committee
alumni association
It depends on the day of
before the hour
Hmm
exaggeration
chau
Kun
Hmm
world
in some cases
I made up my mind
from now on
Ken Uesugi
world
I made you wait
is
why are you here
I came to see you
world
Hey
Lie
is
this is impossible
It's okay
why did this happen
but I turned quite a lot
why weren't you here
Because
come to me
I bought freshly made
It's the voucher you gave me
village
square
of
I've been waiting for you
I decided to be you and the sky here
Hmm
So
After getting this result
I will listen
You are
sorry
here we go
Mr. Miss
Even so, I've gathered courage
If it is said that there is a shortage
Mr. Uesugi is me
is very
What is it
actual
for
better
there must be people
is
Me
I want to fit in somehow
do not have
What does it mean
this
teeth
not me
Everyone
of
But
Everyone
i'm listening to you now
tell me how you feel
That bastard
made use of
Uesugi-kun
Itsuki
They
I tried to run to my unlucky mother
There should be one place you should go
Excessive care only hurts
That's right
Suma
Yotsuba
she always said
again and again
Persistent
do not have
increase
Hey
I invite you to a school trip that will never happen this time
mm
from regret
don't make it a school festival
Then don't give up
ah
Like
now
to
teeth
the typhoon is
rice field
I can't be the only one special
Me
Something
This is Fuchu
was
excuse me
for now
bus
do you want to ride home
keep the way it opens
everyone used it
Let me tell you what I have
this 200 yen
don't lend
I know it
Be careful
it's gone
orange
in poverty
5 every time
it's a yen
I'm strong
It's not hard without money
Hmm
What does it mean
master
number
Hey
for the family
Your mother works alone
so
I sometimes think
I need a lot number
she was happy with her mother
because she
she will study a lot
she got smarter
Exceptional
lightweight manners
Join a company that gives
mother is
let me
then surely
I think there's meaning in me
Awesome
such as pretone
Various
I study hard too
get smarter
when you start making money
I might be able to let my little sister live a comfortable life.
I wonder if I can become a necessary person
Man
we are mother
for Mr.
mother sister
for
study hard
Hmm
100 yen each for me and you
thank you god
Hmm
four leaves
that ribbon
you look good
Thank you
I can't be mistaken for everyone
here we go
what do you think
what are you wearing
not a big difference
that
not only
world
Me
learn from everyone
It was the best before
Me
teeth
Exactly
baby
cute
imitate them
want to see
Hey
Yotsuba
your efforts are great
nothing wrong
but
without being number one
you
each person is special
as a parent
i want you to be with me
no matter what happens
it doesn't matter where you are
to be human
excuse me
to talk like this
It's my first time
you guys
I take responsibility
Mom
we became junior high school students
older sister
together
Impossible
we
I can no longer be the author
previous test
most of people
well said
I was invited to join the track and field club, but I turned it down.
But I want to concentrate on my studies so it can't be helped
I want to encourage you
Hmm
what
it's cold
If she was a mom, she'd give me more compliments
she will praise
Taro's present time
are you studying
four leaves
This doesn't work either
is
You'll get in the way of studying
May I borrow this
It's getting better and better
more from him
yo four leaves
history test
teeth
I scored like this
A game borrowed from four leaves
thanks to
Football
Tane
I have to try harder
study a lot
get smarter
Exceptional
A company that pays
I
what should i study for
The important thing that doesn't have to be special
because it's about being human
why is it important to be
I don't understand
no
Nara Girls High School
school
land
everyone in the department
Mr. Miss
I'm stopped by everyone
needed by many people
none of the sisters
Just me
what is it
Lately I've been practicing all the time, but I'm fine
I can study
If you'd like
let me tell you
I'm all
Wrong
won't be together
I
I'm number seven in the play
I wonder if it's different
Failed make-up exam
Yotsuba Nakano
fail you
such
yes
is
right
it's not a lie
only
Even though it was
this
vertical path
no pond from
I should have warned you again
You didn't try to quit the multiple entry club
pack your bags
an acquaintance of mine serves as director
at a coed school
From the beginning of summer vacation
you will go there
Me
is it
I should be special
Trying to make a meaning for me
I came here desperately
Me
what a single
when you're alone
what should i do
I can be special tomorrow
To
i don't know if
If Yatsuba transfers schools
we will follow
What are you saying
Neighborhood in a hurry
true intentions
I was able to pass
running
thanks to
Year
of
okay
we can
is
Everyone
for me
To
guy
I don't know what you think
I definitely don't want you to leave
We're all together wherever we go
that is
Is it your mother's fault
four leaves
no matter what
we are all five
because it's a minute
Such
People can overcome
your mother said
she was saying
hey
Stop thinking about who's the best
Then
i live for everyone
Taker
now i
thanks to all my sisters i'm here
memory
is
Raw
It's the department
all the sisters are good guys
Awesome
with the guy
I love them
that I was their tutor
I am proud
But
without you
I was especially empty
Such a thing
'Cause I'm a weak man
I'll keep stumbling over and over again
This is my selfish wish
Yotsuba at that time
I'm happy to have you next to me
don't worry
you are my support
i want to support you
So if you don't like it, that's fine
let me know how you feel
Me
rabbit
this
let's get around
i hate moon
killer
clean
is
Me
teeth
Lie
turn on
not
I liked it
excuse me
I still have to do something
aren't you dating
actually
Wow
i'm not dating
that's six
Mr. Taro Honfu
nobody's
Crispy
to be
You said you liked Yotsuba
then quantity
Moe
Then
I'll be hated if I brood over it
I guess
Thanks
deer
even if you
Even if the day comes when
However
it was us
what you really said
now i know
I've been
I should have liked you
They are
I should have picked you up yesterday
I don't want you to worry about me now
I was worried
really important family
in that case
we you say so far
If this relationship continues
Sheet
let me cut
four leaves
If I stay in a place like this all the time, my body will get cold
my four leaves
what
I thought
I won't be chosen
Create a date with Fuutarou
I wonder
No good
ethically
ah
place
mosquito
just us karaoke
to come
It's my first time
yo four leaves
To
because it's a consultation
The fact that I am disguised as Yotsuba
is
Even if I can imitate Yotsuba
I can't become a yotsuba
this juice
teeth
too sweet for me
but i'm angry
if i were
I won't do anything to embarrass Fuutarou
You're at a loss for an answer
Yotsuba becomes Fuutarou
I thought you liked me a little
I'm not lost
my feelings haven't changed since long ago
I keep thinking about Uesugi-san
All the more so
there should be no reason to hesitate
You're worried about school before you lived together, right?
don't worry about us
it's okay to date
what
i thought i would say
Somehow I knew
nevertheless
frustrating things are frustrating
no matter what
emotions get irritated
I was that serious
if
It was the same with four leaves
this feeling of ours
I want you to accept
real feelings
i didn't understand
it's natural to be angry
Nino
was in
in love
We are neither enemies nor friends
I see
if you think so
at least resistance
definitely
I won't give you a push on my back
It's a good start
rice field
Hey you
listen
Miku
I will definitely sing better
desired place
right hand
To
As expected, if you keep asking men
I didn't think
rice field
older sister
Me
i miss you all
I misunderstand one of the four leaves
this is dare
I won't tell the four leaves, but
That time
Because I chose to come to my current school
I met Fuutarou
at least i
i don't think it's unfortunate
Because I met Fuutarou
I
from
teeth
I
I couldn't become Yotsuba
Yotsuba can't be me
at last
as much as you think
i fell in love with me
Moon
can i have a minute
na
what is it
what i want to talk about
it's not good here
then here
talk to me
Corner
not
Don `t worry
I feel softly
This chest moyamoya
teeth
Are vacant
Yotsuba has begun to create a place for us quintuplets.
you
buy the ground
Hey
Thinking with my brother who was yesterday
just pushing
However
I still think the same
my wish is
Amazed
Even though you still say such sweet things
I admit
dead
rat
mouse or rat
there is
hey
After all, prefectures are strict
please stay away
Such a place
I can show you to the quatrefoils
Lunch break will be over
I'm going home
I came to tell you with my own determination
my wish is
To have my relationship with Mr. Uesugi recognized
Head down with
that
not now
months
I don't know how long it will take
how much i love uesugi sa
this
strength of thought
I want you to
yes
Even if the current you apologizes or persuades me
I can't believe you
knowing that
You're going to take the road of thorns, aren't you?
I
As much as I love Uesugi-san
Because I like everyone in the play
not at all
I don't know
It seems to be Takeda four leaves
Released from the shackles of the quintuplets, they push forward
I don't like your back
I was envious
you still me
Do you see me as a rival to you?
sure
we
We'll live while being conscious of each other all the time
sometimes friends
sometimes a waterfall
rival
Hey you
The battle isn't over here
I'll watch over your future from a little behind
If I show you that I like you even a little
I wonder if you'll just take me away
hey
I wonder if it's about time
Hey, please take over two people who have already done
did you notice
maybe forever
You were good
yes
because it means
Yume Yume Don't let your guard down
I'll keep that in mind
You ended up putting out your hand in trouble
but
I can say that I did it with this
you
Not alone
Uesugi-kun
Congrats
actually invited
thank you
bad for holidays
such
I'm happy
Really
Somehow
We couldn't be alone at school
surely
where who
i don't know from
practiced
to the customer
this
not the other way around
mother
is
here we go
You can order whatever you want as much as you like
it's my treat
that was good
frustrating
dating
destination is family restaurant
Nanoyo
good inn
please
coupon
I'm using
eye-catching
Coupon at
Toka ng
is
For Fuutarou, you're the one who did your best.
If you think
I'm getting a recommendation from a sports college.
yes
Then
after all
dreams
some sport
become a player
I forgot my childhood dream
I am after all
someone's support
to support
i think it suits me
It started with giving up
Now I realize that everyone can be proud
it seems like you
I got one
Because Mr. Uesugi said so
yes
is
raw
if i get accepted to university
I want to study so that I can get such a job.
Really
the bad is
library was boring
With Mr. Uesugi
anything is great fun
Then
At the end
just one place
Yatsuba
It looks like you don't have to push your back anymore
It's nostalgic
you
this rag
blank
if you liked
today
teeth
I'm sure Uesugi-san will take you to a place that has a special place in your heart.
A family restaurant that the family sometimes goes to
library for studying
Your time is from that day
here is one of them
Good
It's
really still confused
aside from all my sisters
only
I wonder if it's okay to be happy
mosquito
choice is
I wonder if it's right
you
You just flew from here
show me again
then it's cheap
is for
how is it
Yotsuba
of
if i could fly that far
I have a story to tell you
that
teeth
let's go
death
please don't
look at me
I should be able to go further
one
Such
dating
Because I'm an inexperienced person who can't do one thing
nevertheless
I can be the man who stands next to you
get promoted
the right way
wrong way
let's walk together
that's why
if you like
with me
this is
I like it
marry me
master
is
yes
that's true
more
clean
from the beginning
if you say
world
Me
It's just another story
smartphone
let me start over just one more time
pot
childhood dream
remembered
everyone longed for
I want to hurry
hmm
It's a promise
Surely someday
please make my dream come true
ah
character
fruit
Hana to you
to you
There's something I must say
university i attend
couldn't you say
tokyo rider
I know that
I didn't dare to ask
I guess you
I thought
Hmm
is not it
we don't care at all
ancestor
exam
Good luck
When
I'll go see you too
Thanks
nice to meet you
See you
Also
It was as expected
It was rare to feel lonely
but
maybe a little happy
Uesugi-san
During
is seen
increase
don't cry
I decided
dreams or goals
I wonder if I can be like you
Humans can do it
if we
just a little more
I'll keep you company
Is that so
hmm
come on
It's time to go
death
Me
Hey you
guy
Living alone after college
really not unreasonable
Ichikawa is worried
she was drowning
I'm fine
That's right
we all
I'm nervous without any pain
mosquito
Hey
that's why
i'm not alone
ah
surely
rice
hmm
mm
sometimes
make it soon
Then we will prepare
Gathering after a long time
Hmm
Some countries don't change
Came back
Japan
you were just traveling
Moon
thank you for coming
because you're famous
welcome
you guys
sometimes
long time no see
I'm glad both of you are fine
The shop seems to be thriving too.
As expected of America
Rash is a joke
is good at speaking
real america
How was it when you went to
still intonation
I'm worried about only
sometimes
intonation
It's tough
I guess it's because I'm a teacher
you're going to eat
don't prepare now
or
Hey
America
Anna of
quaint cafe
Will it suit the taste of the person in
I also went to Sue Express
To
teeth
always family inn
star
I'm watching you
hey
it's not
That's it
Then, as a thank you, I will introduce this shop to you.
hand
Buried
If you take advantage of the popularity of the day
The number of customers will definitely increase
I'm very happy
I still refrain from it now
Recently, the number of regular customers has increased.
Lent me this well-equipped place
for your father
I want to do it with our own strength just a little more
na
Noni
proud sister
No matter where I go, I'm not ashamed
If you don't sell well, you can let me work for you
you're not cute
that is cute
Everyone
It's the appearance of today's leading role
all together
why are you sweating
I guess he couldn't sit still and came running from home on his bicycle.
I've been
what just before an important ceremony
I don't care
As expected, Uesugi-kun is a train, isn't he?
Fuutarou has been here since yesterday
so i'm still sleeping
Chan
eh
what
I have to admit this
That's why I secretly read it early in the morning
my makeup
thank you for coming
very
what are you scared of
You didn't want to ride it, did you?
Uesugi-kun must make sure
Day
I want to wear it This is our wedding present
mother's keepsake earrings
The guy
I can guarantee
Hey you
please
ok then
world
Hey
Nah
no
groom
The bride's relatives have arrived
Was good
I thought you weren't coming
why didn't you come to the ceremony
sorry
to come or not
I was thinking about it until just before
I don't deserve to be called your father
please come
thank you
In the past, many rudeness due to youth was too profitable
ask straight
yes
Everyone who Tsubasa is sincerely pleased with
me too
wine
receive
yes
I'm back
Fuutarou's Waiting Room
my mother died
more than ten years ago
the accident happened
It was just after her mother's dream of opening her own restaurant.
was left inside
Only a large amount of debt borrowed for start-up funds
father never again
To
That vacant store is in Kashitaru
half to help them
and half
It may have been to entrust her mother's dream
love one woman for the rest of one's life
I want to be that kind of man
is like the father of
will finance
right
excuse me
i'm not used to it
I don't want to be called my father
groom
the bride is calling
Please come
Um
go ahead
eh
marlowe
world
I'm old too
Wasn't alcohol only used for celebrations?
That's it
that's why i'm drinking
Those guys
i think it will work
such a thing
It's not something parents can decide
however
It is certain that it will not be easy
anyway the opponent
because she's my daughter
yes
that
I can tell
ladies and gentlemen
busy today
Thank you for joining us at our wedding reception
Thank you very much
so beautiful
again
Like a four-leaf handle
Wedding with such fun
dress
I want to wear it
do you know what you're doing
Sure it's a little complicated
I said sweet things
moreover
It's not wasabi
Even this is Hanayama's exclusive
Sadao Abe
is in a position
Me
Speaking of worries, I
Wind Taro
you know
Then
fool
bastard
When I think I've become a sensible adult
I was relieved that it seemed to be the same
lick me
Omae Maeda
again
thank you family
I'm here today
father
teeth
As expected
thanks to all my sisters
I'm glad that my father became my father
you have a day
Ichikawa, the eldest daughter
She is a big sister who brings us all together.
As you know, she is a very successful actress.
my
It is an existence of longing
I was surprised by your sister.
It's nostalgic
The roundabout was quite difficult
Cool
beauty
What in the world are you singing
i won't be fooled
stupidity
indulge in drowsiness
Taida
world
even if you don't say that
nevertheless
The appearance of trying to be strong
i can't see it dazzling
that's a big plus
Hey
you're next
Brother
then what
A little angry
soggy
strictly
You are the older sister who pushes us on the back.
Then my power is outstanding
I have to follow suit too
Is it the rest of my life?
yes yes
Was good
hey
at a time like this
all you have to do is give
your strength
The flip side of that one-fold weakness
rigor
Because there is so much love
I used to be
couldn't find the answer
yes
I
do
Really
make
I guess
three of the company
teeth
It's not like Fushigi and her older sister
It may be close to a close friend who has been in contact with you in the same position
that's why
Meat that made my dreams come true
I am joining
I get anxious sometimes
Me
I wonder if I'm doing well
I don't even have to answer
you've always fought yourself like that
The result I won
it's definitely your fault
believe in yourself
you're old man
I thought you would say that
direction
If so
The rest is Komaeda
find
I
four
only
What
hey
Then
it's a good month
is dead
When is
Cute motor that I can only be a big sister
is
actually more than me
I've been doing it properly
When I'm wondering what to do
The one who gave me a push on my back
it's the moon
let it run
hand
At this time, let me say
since i met you
my life started to go crazy
period relationship
Industry curry
It's okay
I
Such delicacy until I meet you
I could not imagine that there are people without
head big natural wood
After all, you are unlikely to be a match for the rest of your life
Moon
medium i return to tone
I can't help it
Against Fuutarou
Even with this, I'm living to the fullest
and you
It's four leaves
is
all my sisters were gone
my life was completely different
I also felt that there were many things called quintuplets
Hey
Sheet
hundreds of times
I still have fun memories
If you've been dating for this long, you'll remember even if you don't like it
i was a tutor
I learned a lot from you
I met you quintuplets
I'm one of the few people I'm proud of
I
Being able to be born as quintuplets sisters with everyone
I was happy
A little different from other houses
It may look strange to people.
I
i love that kind of family
five years
This is finally the end
I also got rid of the thread of tension and got tired all at once
You were nervous too, weren't you?
Wind Taro
not as much
kiss of oath
and stipulated blu blu
was
That can't be helped
everyone is watching
even with you
i remember a year ago
that is after all
bride
I forgot something in the waiting room
thank you
increase
sorry
I don't need it anymore
please throw it away
Understood
is it ok
trademark
mud
Good
I don't know
you
each person is special
I cheat sometimes
there is someone who notices me
Hmm
what are you doing
Gatera-sama
i liked it
if it is decided
One thing to do after the ceremony
travel or
mother
to
I was going to follow you
rice field
Because I'm worried about where it's going
these guys are extreme
It's more fun when we're all together
here we go
Who
I want to go
Yotsuba says so
I couldn't drink for the same thing before
then let's go
Hmm
Kyu Uesugi wake up
good morning
increase
Watching Fuutarou made me sleepy too
If you catch a cold, don't sleep in such a place and get up early
the wedding
what
you're quick
don't be half asleep forever
Four quick decisions
Man
trip
Graduation trip
Fuutarou suggested it.
Lie
in this case
5 for the time being
It's a human pointing
You know my opinion
I think I should stop too
See you soon
Hey
Ryoma Sakamoto Ugly
It's no different than a school trip, isn't it?
from Okinawa and
Hokkaido has a lot of delicious food.
hey
There are many nice places
cocoa
Chan
Nice to meet you back then
hmm
Quintuplets are troublesome
Dana
I don't know
Ta
Hey hey hey hey hey
hey
Ya
now
world
for a moment
boy
Hey
Naa
nice
Good
Hey
Then
Good
Hey hey hey
hey
no
car
Hey
Good
no
Then
Good
Hey
no
Good
Then
Hey you